Indiana University Bureau of Public Discussion Director's records, 1956-1977 C340
Indiana University Archives
- Conferences and seminars, 1963-1976
  - 12th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy – Readings, 1970 (Box 6)
  - 13th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy –, May 2-4, 1971 (Box 6)
  - 14th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy – General, October 8-10, 1972 (Box 7)
  - 14th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy- Selection of Participants, 1972 (Box 7)
  - 15th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy, May 20-22, 1976 (Box 7)
  - National Foreign Policy Conference for Educators, Washington D.C., June 16, 1966 (Box 7)
  - National Foreign Policy for NGO's Department of State Conference, 1966 (Box 7)
  - NGO Conference: Department of State, 1968 (Box 7)
  - National Foreign Policy Conference for NGO's, 1969 (Box 7)
  - State Department Foreign Policy Conference for Nongovernmental Organizations, September 18-19, 1972 (Box 7)
  - State Department Foreign Policy Conference for Nongovernmental Organizations, March 28-29, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Regional Foreign Policy Conference, November 1963 (Box 7)
  - Secretary of State's National Foreign Policy Conference for Educators, June 20-21, 1968 (Box 7)
  - South Bend Workshop on Foreign Policy, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Ft. Wayne Seminar on Foreign Trade, December 6-7, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Seminar on Indiana University's Problem Solving Ability, May 18, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Gary Conference on International Human Rights, October 23, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Gary International Human Rights Conference, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Indianapolis Workshop, International Human Rights, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Gary International Trade Conference, April 1973 (Box 7)
  - Indianapolis Conference on International Trade, Program Development, Winter 1974 (Box 7)
  - International Trade Conference (Box 7)
    - Basil Kafiris, April 1972 (Box 7)
    - Evaluations, October 19-20, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Registrations, October 19, 1972 (Box 7)
  - IUPUI International Trade Conference, Spring 1975 (Box 7)
  - Midwest International Trade Conference, Selection of Participants, April 25-30, 1972 (Box 7)
  - Midwest Conference on United States and International Trade (Box 7)
    - New Developments and Prospects, April 28-29, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Highly Industrialized Western Countries and Japan, October 19-20, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Roster of Participants, October 19-20, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Selection of Participants, October 19-20, 1972 (Box 7)
    - October 19-20, 1972 (Box 8)
    - October 20, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Conference for Land Use Planners, Spring 1975 (Box 8)
  - Land Use in Southern Indiana: New Directions, April 9, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Land Use Planning in Southern Indiana, April 9, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Land Use in Central Indiana Where do we grow from here?, November 1975 (Box 8)
  - Form Letters and Fliers for Land Use in Central Indiana, November 1975 (Box 8)
  - Land Use in Northwestern Indiana, Proposed Conference, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Land Use Conference in Northern Indiana, June 9, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Land Use in South Quarter Indiana, New Albany, Winter 1976 (Box 8)
  - Conference on Latin America, Indianapolis, Indiana, April 15, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Indianapolis Leadership Conference, June 1967 (Box 8)
  - Kokomo Mayor's Conference, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Midwest Nations, Inc. Workshop, Summer 1968 (Box 8)
  - Third Methodist Seminar for Continuing Education for Ministers, January 17-18, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Forth Annual Seminar for Methodist Ministers (Box 8)
    - 1968 (Box 8)
    - Printed Program and Instructional Roster, Newspaper Coverage (Box 8)
    - Correspondence and Memos (Box 8)
    - Participant List, Menus, Conference Bureau (Box 8)
    - Reading Lists, Outlines, etc. (Box 8)
    - Seminar Appraisal Information (Box 8)
  - Seminar on Sex Research for Methodist Ministers, January 25, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Fifth Annual Seminar on Continuing Education for Methodist Ministers, April 1969 (Box 8)
  - Seminar for Methodist Ministers, April 14-15, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Conference for Ministers, April 17-19, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Council on Ministries Office Conference, October 1-3, 1975 (Box 8)
  - National University Extension Association, Miami Beach, July 20, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Neighborhood Workers Training Program, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Midwest Political Science Association Conference, April 30-May 2, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Conference on Population Problems, Spring 1975 (Box 8)
  - Populations Conference, April 1975 (Box 8)
  - Population Problems in the U.S. and other Rich Western Countries, May 1975 (Box 8)
  - Population Problems in the U.S. and other Rich Western Countries, Registrants, May 1975 (Box 8)
  - Population, Hunger, and the Interruptible Contract Between Nature and Society, October 2-3, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Private Rights and the Public Interest, Columbus, October 1975 (Box 9)
  - Workshop on Planning Program Budgeting Systems, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Columbus Program Planning Workshop, February 4-5, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Program on Providing the Public Goods and Services for a Quality Way of Life, Fort Wayne, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Second Annual Clay County Seminar on Public Affairs, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Shortridge Soulweek, March 23-27, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Social Studies Project, South Bend, February 1971 (Box 9)
  - Southern Indiana Conference, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Southern Indiana Inc. Conference, May 18, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Mid-American United Nations Conference, 1969 (Box 9)
  - United Nations Speakers Bureau, 1970 (Box 9)
  - United Nations in a World on Conflict, Fort Wayne, December 4-5, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Gary United Nations Day Conference, 1971 (Box 9)
  - The Task of Universities in a Changing World, Notre Dame Conference, April 16-19, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Gary: Model Cities – Urban Affairs Conference, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Utilization of Wastes, Spring 1976 (Box 9)
  - Kokomo Conference on Waste Disposal, April 21, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Conference #754A-67 West European Studies, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Midwest Conference on West European and Atlantic Studies (Box 9)
    - January 14-15, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Budget, January 14-15, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Francois Fontaine, January 14-15, 1966 (Box 9)
- Program and course files, 1961-1977
  - African Art Exhibit, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - African Literature Course – Emile Snyder, 1969 (Box 9)
  - African Programs, 1970 (Box 9)
  - African Studies (Box 9)
    - Black Theatre Scripts, undated (Box 9)
    - Camp Otto, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Columbus, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Columbus Continuing Education Course, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - Continuing Education Program, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - Focus: Black America, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Kerner Commission Report, Home Study Program, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Kerner Report Workshop, 1968 (Box 9)
    - Muncie, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Programs, 1970 (Box 9)
      (Restricted and Financial Records were removed and destroyed)
    - Program Development, 1972-1974 (Box 9)
    - Publicity, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Sister Mary Theresa O'Neill, 1970 (Box 9)
    - TV/Press Africa Material, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - TV Programs(SSN's), 1969 (Box 9)
    - University Faculty with Interest, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Afro-American Short Course- Survey of Afro-American Art, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Tour of Art Institute (cancelled), 1976 (Box 10)
  - Art Institute of Chicago Tour, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Arts and Society Program, 1967 (Box 10)
  - Binford Junior High School, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Bloomington and Monroe County Development Program, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Bloomington Water Operators Certifications Program (Box 10)
    - Enrollments, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - General, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Instructions, forms, and completed reports, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Mathematics Manual, 1975 (Box 10)
  - United States Policy Toward China and Southeast, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - United States Policy Toward China and Southeast Asia, Home Study Program (Box 10)
    - 1968 (Box 10)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 10)
    - 1974 (Box 10)
  - Possible China Speakers, 1967; undated (Box 10)
  - Citizens Exchange Corps, 1967 (Box 10)
  - Civil Defense, 1970-1973 (Box 10)
  - Clarksville- New Albany Your, Noncredit Course, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Columbus Architectural Course, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Columbus Architectural Course- Appraisal Forms, 1969; (includes photos) (Box 10)
  - Columbus Architecture Lecture Series, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Columbus Black Arts Festival(SSN's), 1970 (Box 10)
  - Columbus Contemporary Drama Program(SSN's), 1969 (Box 10)
  - Columbus Possible Programs, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Columbus Service League- School System Programs and the Precocious Child, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Community Service Council of Metropolitan Indianapolis, Inc., 1966 (Box 10)
  - Crime Reduction and the Attainment of Justice: Imperatives in America?- Noncredit Course, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Criminal Justice, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Criminal Justice Course- Noncredit Course, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Defense Information School, 1967 (Box 10)
  - Discussion Mobile, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - The Dying Art of Criticism, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Electoral Politics- Noncredit Course, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Energy Crisis Short Course, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Environmental Programs, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Gary: Model Cities, 1968 (Box 11)
  - General Geologic Highlights with Emphasis on the Midwest, Short Course, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Green County Course, 1972 (Box 11)
  - High School Curriculum Center in Government, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Indiana Youth Council, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Indiana Forum, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Indianapolis Downtown Campus, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Intercom, 1964-1965 (Box 11)
  - International Education Act, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Kenner Commission Report Home Study Program, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Noncredit Short Courses on Kissinger, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Kruze Lecture, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Labor Foreign Study Tours for Union Officers, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Latin American Study Programs, 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - TEXCATL Reflections of Latin America, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Manchester College, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Mini University, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Mini University, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Mini University, 1975; (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Mini University, 1976; (3 folders) (Box 11)
  - Mini University, 1977; (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Project MARC Selective Dissemination Experiment- Dr. Robert W. Hattery, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Noncredit Courses First Semester, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Noncredit Courses Second Semester, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Nonwestern Studies Project, 1963-1968 (Box 11)
  - Ross Allen Opera Appreciation, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Program Planning Letters, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Possible Programs: School Integration, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Public Affairs Forum Noncredit Course, 1975-1976 (Box 11)
  - Public Affairs Forum Notice Program, 1976 (Box 11)
  - The Right to Know to Withhold and to Lie Noncredit Course, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
  - Sounds of Africa, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Terrorism and Anarchy, Noncredit Course Announcements, undated (Box 11)
  - University Series, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Urban Semester, 1967 (Box 11)
  - WFIU Radio Programs, 1961-1966 (Box 11)
  - Wills, Inheritance and Estate Planning, Evening Division Non-credit Courses, 1972-1973 (Box 11)